[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
So classifiers are really trying to make decisions.
分类器的确是用来做决策的
Decisions as to whether a sentence is positive or negative, or
这些决策包括 一个句子是积极的还是消极的
whether a set of lab tests plus x-rays
是否一系列的实验测试
plus measurements lead to a certain disease like flu or cold.
把X光加到治疗当中 会导致一个像流感或者伤寒这样的疾病
That's a decision that needs to be made.
这就是一个我们需要做出的决策
So let's talk a little bit about how classifiers especially linear classifiers
那么我们来讨论一下分类器是怎样通过特定的线性分类器来
make decisions.
做决策的
To understand decision boundaries,
要理解决策边界
suppose you only had two words with non-zero weight.
假设你只有两个权值不为0的单词
You have awesome with positive weight of one and
一个单词是“awesome” 权值为+1
awful which is just awful so it has a negative weight of 1.5.
另一个单词是“awful” 权值为 -1.5
If you have this situation then the score is gonna be 1 times the number of
在这种情况下，评分就由1乘以这个句子中“awesome"的数量
awesomes in the sentence, minus 1.5 times the number of awfuls.
减去1.5乘以“awful”的数量
So we can plot this on an axis, there's the awesome axis and
你可以画出坐标轴，这是“awesome”坐标轴
then there's the awful axis.
这个是“awful”坐标轴
So for example, the sentence, the sushi was awesome,
例如 这个句子 寿司是非常棒的
the food was awesome, but the service was awful.
食物非常棒 但是服务很糟糕
Then that has two awesomes and one awful.
句子中有两个“awesome”和一个“awful”
It's plotted in the point (2,1) on the axis.
因此我们在图上画出 (2,1) 点
And similarly for something that has say, three awfuls and one awesome,
同样的，如果有个句子含有3个“awful”和1个“awesome”
and for something that is all awesome, so three awesomes is at a point (3,0),
如果都是“awesome” 3个“awesome”就画在 (3,0) 点
and so on for other sentences.
其他的句子也是这样
Now, let's understand a little better how we scored the sentences and
现在 让我们了解一下我们是怎样对句子进行评分的
what does that imply about our decisions.
以及怎么推断结论
So, for example, take the point (3,0) as 3 awesomes, no awfuls.
例如，(3,0) 点代表的是有3个“awesome”，而没有“awful”出现
Three awesomes gives you a positive
3个“awesome”给你一个积极的预测
prediction because the score is greater than zero.
因为这个评分是大于0的
And that is true for every point really on the bottom right of the axis.
落在坐标右下侧的所有点都是符合这个规律的
While the points on the top left all have score less than zero so for
而落在坐标左上侧的点因为评分小于0
example the point three awfuls, one awesome got score less than zero.
例如这个有3个“awful” 1个“awesome”的点的评分小于0
So, those get labeled negative.
因此我们标记这些点是负类
And, in fact, what separates the negative predictions from the positive predictions
事实上 把正类和负类分开的
is the line that defines the places where I don't know what's positive and
是当我们不知道这个是正类还是负类的点的集合组成的一条连线
what's negative, and that's the line where 1.0 #awesome- 1.5 #awful = 0.
这条线就是 “1.0 * #awesome - 1.5 * #awful = 0” 所表示的线
And that's the line when, I don't know, the prediction is uncertain, and
这条线就是我们无法做出正类和负类判别决策的线
so we call that the decision boundary.
我们把这条线叫做决策边界
Everything on one side we predict is positive,
在其中一侧的所有点都判定为正类
everything on the other we predict is negative.
在另一侧的所有点都判定为负类
Now notice that the decision boundary,
这个例子中的决策边界
1.0 times awesome minus 1.5 times awful equals to 0 is a line.
“1.0 * #awesome - 1.5 * #awful = 0” 是一条直线
And so that's why it's called a linear classifier.
这也是我们叫它线性分类器的原因
It's a linear decision boundary.
这是一个线性决策边界
So decision boundaries are what separate the positive
决策边界将正类
predictions from the negative predictions.
和负类的预测分开
So, in the case of just two features, we see this is just a line.
在这个只有两种特征的例子中 我把决策边界看作只是一条直线
But that situation will differ as we increase the number of features.
如果我们增加特征的数目 情况就会不同了
So in two dimensions, a linear function is a line.
在二维平面中 线性方程是一条直线
In three dimensions, we have three, words for example that have non-zero weight and
在三维平面中 例如 我们有三个权值不为0的单词
everything else has zero weight and we get to the plane.
除了这三个单词为其他的权值为0 我们会得到一个平面
And so it's a little hard to draw in 3D, but
画一个3D的图形有一点麻烦
the positive predictions here are above the plane and the negative predictions
正类的预测平面的上面 而负类的预测
here are below the plane and the plane is somehow inclined in the space.
在平面的下方，这个平面是与空间呈一定倾角的
Now when you have not just three non-zero words but in
如果权值不为0的单词数目不只是3个
re-application you're gonna have tens of thousands of words with non-zero weight.
可能有成百上千个单词的权值不为0
And in that case we'll call those hyperplanes,
在这种情况下 我们叫这个决策边界为超平面
really high dimensional separators called hyperplanes.
在非常高的纬度正负类的分离器 叫做超平面
Now, of course you can use more than linear classifiers.
当然 这种情况下 你就不能使用线性分类器了
You can use more complex classifiers.
你可以使用更加复杂的分类器
And those, instead of having lines or
在那些分类器之中 决策边界不是简单的直线
hyperplanes, they have more complicated shapes or squiggly separations.
而是超平面 他们有更复杂的形状 或者弯弯曲曲的形状
And we're gonna learn more about that in the classification course.
我们在分类的课程中 会学到更多相关知识
>> [MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: dalongraymond | 审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translate Community